So we can actually make this even
shorter. Um, so if you're ever if you're
only ever taking a single input as a
parameter, there's a way you can make it
shorter. The other way you can make it
shorter is if you can return all of the
work that you've done on a single line,
then you can make it shorter. So we're
going to start with that one. Um, I'm
going to comment this out and show you
how you could make it shorter. So, we're
going to say let clean up string equal
messy string. And then I'm going to put
the arrows. And then instead of putting
curly braces here, I'm just going to
type
messy string.trim.2
uppercase.
This does the exact same thing as a line
above it. Because we do because we so
often write functions that do a single
piece of work and then we immediately
return that work. We've said the return
here is implied. Um if you're only doing
a single piece of work, it's pretty much
implied that that's what you're going to
return. So you can get rid of the return
and the curly braces if you just um
write a single line of code that you
want to return. So now this takes in a
messy string, trims it, uppercases it,
and returns it. And we've gotten rid of
the word return and the curly braces.
Well, you can also make this shorter if
you're only taking a single piece of
input. Um,
you don't need the parenthesis. So you
can just say let clean up string equal
messy string. And then because we put
this arrow here, we already know it's
going to be a function. And we already
know that functions take input, which
means we don't really need the
parentheses around this. We can just
take this and we'll just imply that the
parenthesis are there. And then on the
other side of it, we'll return messy
string.trim
to uppercase. And so now in a single
line, we've said we're going to create a
function called cleanup string. It's
going to take messy string as an input.
It's going to trim it and it's going to
uppercase it. And then it's going to
return it. We don't need the keyword
return because it's implied because
we're only doing a single line of
processing, which implies that we're
going to want to return what we
processed. We don't need parenthesis
because this arrow here already tells us
it's a function and we're already only
receiving one input. If we were
receiving two inputs, um, like second
input, then we would need the
parenthesis
because we're going to put a comma there
and commas um, need to be inside of
those parenthesis. But because we aren't
receiving more than one line of input or
one thing of input, we can just receive
messy string. Um, and we don't need the
parenthesis. And now we don't have to
type the word function. We don't have to
type the opening and closing
parenthesis. We don't have to type the
opening and closing curly braces. And we
don't even need to type the word return.
All of this is all simplified down to a
single line. In the next video, I'll
show you why you might want to do